

Junior .Net Developer specializing in Desktop and Web development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including C#, HTML5, JavaScript, CSS, MS SQL. Experienced in project management and customer relations.

SUKHROB KUDRATOV

Age: 24

Nationality: Uzbekistan

Phone: +998 93 992 47 96

E-Mail: kudratovsuhrob@gmail.com

GitHub: github.com/futuricon

Skills

Programming Languages

C#	
JavaScript	
HTML/CSS	
SQL	

Frameworks & Technologies

.NET	
ASP.NET Core	
WPF	
Entity Framework	
Bootstrap	
jQuery	
Git	

Software

Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Git, Photoshop, Illustrator

Languages

Uzbek – C2 Russian – C2 English – B2

Experience

04/2021 to 07/2021

Web Developer - Freelance, Uzbekistan

- Full stack web developer responsible for end-to-end web app development.
- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.
- Worked closely with client to provide a customized website for their business.

05/2020 to 04/2021

IT-specialist - Green City, Uzbekistan

- Handled all desktop support issues in a high-volume manufacturing firm.
- Installed, services and upgraded over 30 Windows computers.
- Work with senior IT-specialist to manage large, complex problems and issues in work process.

•

10/2019 to 05/2020

Desktop App Developer - Diamond Solutions, Uzbekistan

- Developed various desktop applications using .NET stack (WPF, EF Core)
- Designed UI and UX for WPF applications.
- Experience in teamwork and in using Git.

Education

2017-2021

Tashkent University of Information Technologies Samarkand, Uzbekistan

- Bachelor of Science
- Major: Software Engineering